A Guide to the Papers of Kenneth W. Thompson 10/22/2002
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Group IV: Articles
  - New York Times 1972 Mar 12 (Box-folder 20:129)
  - Orbis 1959 winter (Box-folder 20:129)
  - Political Science Quarterly-- 9 articles 1956 Sep - 1973 Sep (Box-folder 20:130)
  - Pulpit Digest 1960 Nov (Box-folder 21:131)
  - Review of Politcs-- 4 articles 1952 Oct - 1956 Oct (Box-folder 21:131)
  - Review...-- 3 articles 1958 Oct - 1967 Apr (Box-folder 21:132)
  - Review...-- 3 articles 1968 Jan - 1971 Jul (Box-folder 21:133)
  - Review...-- 3 articles 1972 Apr - 1973 Jul (Box-folder 21:134)
  - Review... 1973 Jul (Box-folder 21:135)
  - Review of Religious Research 1960 fall (Box-folder 21:135)
  - RF Illustrated 1973 Nov (Box-folder 21:135)
  - Saturday Review-- 4 articles 1963 Nov 30 - 1965 Aug 3 (Box-folder 21:135)
  - Saturday Review-- 7 articles 1965 Sep 18 - 1968 Oct 12 (Box-folder 21:136)
  - Scarsdale Inquirer-- 5 articles 1965 Aug 26 - 1971 Apr 4 (Box-folder 21:136)
  - Scope-- 2 articles 1966 May - Nov (Box-folder 21:136)
  - Social Research-- 2 articles 1958, 1960 winter, autumn (Box-folder 21:136)
  - Union Seminary Quarterly Review 1956 Jan (Box-folder 22:137)
  - United Church Herald Reviews-- 3 articles 1959 Oct 29 - 1962 Oct 16 (Box-folder 22:137)
  - VISTA 1973 Feb (Box-folder 22:137)
  - World Alliance Newsletter-- 4 articles 1956 Apr - 1957 Sep (Box-folder 22:137)
  - World Politics 1956 Apr (Box-folder 22:137)
  - World View 1955 Sep (Box-folder 22:137)
  - World View-- 7 articles 1958 Oct - 1971 Jul/Aug (Box-folder 22:138)
- Group V: Christianity and Crisis
  - Correspondence 1957 Oct 25 - 1969 Oct 17 (Box-folder 22:139)
  - Articles 1955 Oct 3 - 1958 Aug 4 (Box-folder 22:140)
  - Articles 1958 Oct 27 - 1960 Mar 7 (Box-folder 22:141)
  - Articles 1960 Jun 13 - 1962 Dec 24 (Box-folder 23:142)
  - Articles 1963 Feb 18 - 1966 Feb 21 (Box-folder 23:143)
  - Articles 1966 Jul 11 - 1967 Nov 27 (Box-folder 23:144)
  - Articles 1967 Dec 25 - 1968 Dec 9 (Box-folder 23:145)
  - Articles 1969 Mar 17 - 1971 Apr 5 (Box-folder 23:146)
- Group VI: Miscellany
  - Twenty-three (23) photographs 1961-1972 (Box-folder 23:146a)
  - American Diplomacy and Emergent Patterns(1962): galley proofs (see Group II) (Box-folder 24:147)
  - Foreign Assistance(1972): galley and page proofs (see Group II) (Box-folder 24:148)
  - Foreign Policies in a World of Change, ed. KWT with Joseph E. Black (1963): partial revision of paper on Japan (see Group II) (Box-folder 24:149)
  - "Cultural Relations for the Future" 1972 Jul 17-23 (Box-folder 24:150)
    mailing list for conference report (see Group III)
  - File Card Index to the Collection (Box 25)